<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-03-30T06:05:21.003Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-03-30T06:05:21.003Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who taught mortals to open portals again?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn4kba/who_taught_mortals_to_open_portals_again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn4kba/who_taught_mortals_to_open_portals_again/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-30T04:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Tesla_taz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, the convenience of public amenities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn2qbv/ah_the_convenience_of_public_amenities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn2qbv/ah_the_convenience_of_public_amenities/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-30T02:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Aetherom  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who taught mortals disintegrate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn1u95/who_taught_mortals_disintegrate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn1u95/who_taught_mortals_disintegrate/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-30T01:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/StressedBYaMtn0books  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorcery is so misunderstood, feel free to discuss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn0ngl/sorcery_is_so_misunderstood_feel_free_to_discuss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn0ngl/sorcery_is_so_misunderstood_feel_free_to_discuss/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-30T00:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ZyreRedditor  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spellcasting advice for a new wizard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn08ew/spellcasting_advice_for_a_new_wizard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn08ew/spellcasting_advice_for_a_new_wizard/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-30T00:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I am a new apprentice wizard. Unfortunately, my master recently got his soul devoured while braving the tenth hell, and so I'm on my own for as far forward as I can scry. Any tips?
    submitted by    /u/Beneficial_Hurry_380  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wizard duel roughs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn00j0/wizard_duel_roughs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jn00j0/wizard_duel_roughs/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-30T00:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Xaalster  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I learn detective sorcery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmzjyc/how_do_i_learn_detective_sorcery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmzjyc/how_do_i_learn_detective_sorcery/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T23:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I get the Grimoire from the detectives? I must acquire knowledge to read people very well and deduce stuff about them. Examples: what type of people they are to know when and what type of cast they spell. I'm willing to learn from the detective sorcerers. Might make art based on this.
    submitted by    /u/Sceptile789  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 AM At SchmArbys sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmx2eg/3_am_at_schmarbys_sequel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmx2eg/3_am_at_schmarbys_sequel/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T21:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Carlharlton2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE GOD HUNTER IS BACK BABY! AND I HUNT WHAT I WANNA!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmwxd3/the_god_hunter_is_back_baby_and_i_hunt_what_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmwxd3/the_god_hunter_is_back_baby_and_i_hunt_what_i/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T21:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/UwU scroll to the bottom if you wanna know wtf this is
 /Rw
 ‎Somedays, I just wanna crush these laws and get away, ah ‎
 ‎I'm growing tired of the antimagic
 ‎ ‎All these people talk but they don't know me, know me, know me, 'cause
 ‎ ‎Ready or not, I call the shots ‎I am the final boss ‎
 ‎You couldn't hunt me, need some more level-ups
 ‎ ‎Don't wanna hear nothing from nobody, nobody, nobody, 'cause
 ‎ ‎It's way too late ‎No way to save the little mass that I used to be ‎
 ‎Your dream will end, it's my time to wake (wooooooooooo~) ‎
 ‎Shu-shu-shu-shut up for a minute ‎'Cause I'm telling you right now ‎
 ‎If you want me ‎
 ‎I ain't easy~
 ‎ ‎Ta-ta-ta-take a cyanide ‎'Cause I like to bring it loud ‎
 ‎And I'm gonna-
 ‎ ‎'Cause I do whatever I wanna ‎'Cause I do what I want ‎'Cause I do wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Title: "Elements of Love"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmwoop/title_elements_of_love/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmwoop/title_elements_of_love/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T21:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title: "Elements of Love"
 The counseling room was cozy, if a bit damp from recent sessions. Granite, an earth elemental with a body of moss-covered stone, sat behind a wooden desk that had seen better days. Across from them sat two clients who, by all logic, should never have been together.
 Pyra, the fire elemental, flickered in shades of gold and crimson, her form barely contained in a vaguely humanoid shape. Every time she got excited, the tips of her flames licked the ceiling. Across from her, Aquon, the water elemental, rippled like a restless tide, his body shifting between a translucent mist and a rolling wave. They were sitting far apart—probably for safety.
 Granite shifted uncomfortably. "So... uh, why don’t you tell me what’s going on?"
 Pyra flared. "He’s suffocating me! Every…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An alert for all e.o.n. member nations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmwduw/an_alert_for_all_eon_member_nations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmwduw/an_alert_for_all_eon_member_nations/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T21:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/WizardswithBlueHelms  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quiet Coup, (R&A related)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmuxcb/the_quiet_coup_ra_related/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmuxcb/the_quiet_coup_ra_related/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T20:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It had been more than a year since Aldin had quietly assumed the burden of the Council’s paperwork, especially in the wake of Masta’s departure. With his unparalleled diligence and mastery of organization, he sifted through mountains of neglected documents, some trivial, others... astonishingly vital. Deeds to farmland, treasury accounts, prisoner transfer orders, artifact vault access protocols—papers that should have had names and signatures attached, but did not. 
 He had done his part. He asked—patiently, persistently—for months, chasing Council members, leaving notices, summoning meetings. Always the same excuses. Always the same avoidance. It had reached a point where progress could no longer wait for bureaucracy. Someone had to sign. 
 And so Aldin had. Over and over, each stroke of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREAT PIT OF ATHRE COLLAPSES!(Cradle prelude)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmutpq/great_pit_of_athre_collapsescradle_prelude/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmutpq/great_pit_of_athre_collapsescradle_prelude/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T20:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Residents of Athre Desert reccomended to flee homes, family, things that resemble sand or dragon corpses
 BREAKING NEWS!
 Today, the Great Pit of Athre, in the centre of the Athre Desert, on the northeastern side of Athret, collapsed. While the cause is yet unknown, three cities so far have fallen into the primordial pit, and the disaster has not stopped! The loss in archeological sites, life, and the general collapsing phenomenon that appears to be ongoing, has lead the State of Athret to issue a travel warning for the desert. This is a dark day for draconic archeology, truly.
 .
 .
 .
 Sand tracks in my scales. Bones fall through my hide. ONWARD. THE CRADLE AWAITS. Yet the Firstblood beckons on, and so do I continue. Crimson, the sand. Silent, the sky. I wish to see the moon.
    submitted by    /u/Drakkonai  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[*With a big Smile.* [R&A MAJOR ANNOUNCEMENT regarding Council.]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmtgg5/with_a_big_smile_ra_major_announcement_regarding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmtgg5/with_a_big_smile_ra_major_announcement_regarding/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T18:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/uw image very related.
 /rw 
 Screen’s across council lands and EON territories that allow either council or R&A transmissions suddenly go black, not a broken black but a video of the dark.
 A loud scraping noise of wood on stone. A piece of furniture being dragged?
 Shortly after Hirk is seen dragging his old ‘physical council seat.’ Built for his size, it is a rather nice chair.
 “Hello my friends.”
 His face is a like a very happy child trying to remain professional.
 He places the chair beside him yet he does not sit.
 “As you all know I am former councillor Hirk MacThors, I had spent many months working to improve and preserve the lives of those within council territory. Of course I also did a bit more but that was out of work hours.”
 “At the time of this speaking my dear friend and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[R&Axit (R&A announcement)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmtato/raxit_ra_announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmtato/raxit_ra_announcement/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T18:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Welcome, everyone. Glad you all came here.”
 Ulrick started uneasily. Big speeches were never really his style. He much preferred to rather listen to them from a shadowy spot.
 There was no time to wait, however. Most of R&A knew he went out to challenge Hirk to make him retake his position, and both of them returned a few days ago.
 Rumors already started spreading, so he had to clear up everything as soon as possible.
 “As probably all of you know, I went out last week when R&A caught whispers of a man eerily similar to Hirk wandering around the countryside.”
 “I intended for him to fight me, to resolve the question of R&A leadership.”
 “And so, we did. We had an official duel for the seat, right in the middle of a ghost town.”
 He glanced across the audience, Relief Force, and many of the “Notable Mages” too. The crowd’s anticipation was almost tangible in the air. Time to deliver the news.
 “We didn’t finish the duel. Instead, Hirk proposed an idea for a new leadership structure.”
 “In the future, R&A would have two leaders: one elected by the people, and one elected by an internal vote. Two heads, overseeing both each other and the organization.”
 “This would not only mean a more stable structure but also lessen the workload of the leader. We’re still sorting out who’d get which tasks.”
 The hall was filled by a swirl of murmurs. Some fearful, some excited. Ulrick had a good guess what most of those were about. Good thing he was just about to address that.
 The true grand news of the day.
 “I know, some of you must be wondering, how a Council wing would have two seats. Would the Council even allow that?”
 “And for that, we have a simple solution. One we’ve been planning for so long.”
 Ulrick put the speech to a short halt, to raise the tension even further. Before dropping the most important declaration of all.
 “We’re going independent from the Council.”
    submitted by    /u/UlrickTheHexblade  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London has since upgraded from knife crime to spell crime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmqs1i/london_has_since_upgraded_from_knife_crime_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmqs1i/london_has_since_upgraded_from_knife_crime_to/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T16:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/reclusivegiraffe  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fairy cats always getting into the spell components.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmqlb9/fairy_cats_always_getting_into_the_spell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmqlb9/fairy_cats_always_getting_into_the_spell/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T16:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/themperorhasnocloth  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come forth neophyte, as friend or enemy. Come forth and allow the tapestry of flesh to be made anew.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmnnqr/come_forth_neophyte_as_friend_or_enemy_come_forth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmnnqr/come_forth_neophyte_as_friend_or_enemy_come_forth/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T14:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Frog_Yeet  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These fucking dragon egg prices.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmngeq/these_fucking_dragon_egg_prices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmngeq/these_fucking_dragon_egg_prices/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T14:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How am I supposed to make a potion now?
    submitted by    /u/Ok_Relief7546  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There is no Horror greater than… Chained Fetch Quests.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmkv49/there_is_no_horror_greater_than_chained_fetch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmkv49/there_is_no_horror_greater_than_chained_fetch/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T12:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kalim huffed in pure annoyance. He needed to recharge the Rod of Resurrection he purchased from Vulkan. To do that he needed Titan’s blood. Ten Suns would trade his Titan’s blood for Leviathan tears. Unfortunately, Kalim didn’t have those but another person had them. Unfortunately that person wanted a bicorn horn. To get the bicorn horn though Kalim would need rainbow pearls. Unfortunately the person with the rainbow pearls wanted the power of Gaia…
 Kalim was quite irritated by the busywork of a CHAINED FETCH QUEST. Seriously he was a fiend from the Nine Hells and not even he was that sadistic. He would track down whatever soul invented the idea of the chained fetch quest and make sure that soul ceased to exist. They were probably already in the Nine Hells for their sadism anyways.
 Kalim stalked along and then paused. Wait a minute… KALIM KNEW A TITAN ALREADY! With tears of joy the Rakshasa flew off to find Atlas and asking for a drop of blood, leaving the Chained Fetch Quest from beyond Hell behind. An hour later he had the blood, which he traded for with Atlas the Titan in exchange for the last bottle of 774 Lemarcia red wine. Expensive? Yes, but so worth it to skip the stupid, stupid, stupid CHAINED FETCH QUEST. Now he just had to find the extixnct race of gem folk that was the target of his Rod of Resurrection.
 Oh and find a specific soul to rend apart. 
    submitted by    /u/AtrioxCalamity  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure magical bloodline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmdw0a/pure_magical_bloodline/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmdw0a/pure_magical_bloodline/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T03:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Level_Hour6480  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil tactical wizard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmcc86/evil_tactical_wizard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmcc86/evil_tactical_wizard/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T02:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Lucian7x  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[✍️✍️✍️]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmbbeo/_/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jmbbeo/_/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-29T01:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/the_frog_mage  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am in awe of this doctrine.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jm6dfb/i_am_in_awe_of_this_doctrine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jm6dfb/i_am_in_awe_of_this_doctrine/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T21:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/krasnogvardiech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is this potential wand too cliché to be my main?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jm2nwu/is_this_potential_wand_too_clich%C3%A9_to_be_my_main/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wizardposting/comments/1jm2nwu/is_this_potential_wand_too_clich%C3%A9_to_be_my_main/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T18:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/H_G_Bells  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wizardposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>